Michael Aulik

4610 Cascade Lane, Minneapolis, MN | 612-483-1505 aulikgage@gmail.com

Summary

Prolific digital, and environmental artist with 5+ years experience. Lifetime passion and experience in games, music and art with exposure in nearly all aspects of design & composition. Adept in working with others to accomplish a common goal.

Experience

PuzzleFox | Minneapolis, Minnesota 3D Artist - Internship | 10/2021 - Present

- Sole designer of various environment and character assets, ensuring all projects were completed in a timely manner
- Illustrated game assets, textured objects and designed & organized multiple environmental areas
- · Regularly communicated lead team to ensure all assets were created to standard and to the clients' needs and requirements
- Collaborated and worked closely with other professionals from the industry; conducted reports on the progress of the projects and presented results to management
- Quickly synthesize feedback and iterate on work to create a desired final product stable for a VR environment

Kirby Gage LLC | Minneapolis, Minnesota

Music Producer, Audio Engineer & Mixed Media Producer | 05/2018 - Present

- Sole operator of Kirby Gage LLC vocal engineering and mixed media creation, such as animation, digital art and music
- · Work with artists nationally and internationally, providing a fast paced and fluid experience to clients
- Lead projects and guide those in the process of creating an album or track
- Responsible for the creation of over 500 production level songs tied to over 10 released records
- High caliber production of digital media including artwork and music when commissioned

Whitethorn Digital | Minneapolis, Minnesota

Artist, Producer & QA - Internship | 05/2021 - 11/2021

- Junior production for music and sound effects for various facets of all games being worked on
- Senior contributor to level design, structure & sound design feedback for full projects within a week or less
- Designated artist and steward for upcoming levels and player interaction within them
- Sole overseer for quality assurance providing a smooth, bug free player experience

Augsburg University | Minneapolis, Minnesota

IT Specialist | 09/2018 - 04/2020

- Simultaneously facilitated over 100 student and faculty account ticket requests regarding account status and private information daily
- Managed the IT front desk and office when required
- Campuswide care and upkeep for all technology under extreme deadlines consistently
- Sole source for manual computer and server side intervention for both student and campus technology

Skills

German, Music Production, Unity & Unreal, 3D Art & Design, Animation, Scripting, Object Oriented Programming, Adobe Suite, Microsoft Office, Blender, FL Studio, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, JSON, JQuery, C++, C#, Python, SQL, Git

Education

Augsburg University | Minneapolis, Minnesota

BA: New Media: Promotional Communication, BA: Game Design | 05/2022

- Graduated summa cum laude—3.6+ GPA
- 7 time deans-list student